<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-02-15T17:34:40+04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/index.xml</id><title type="html">Devops and Devlopment Services</title><subtitle>DevOps &amp; Development strategies &amp; Consulting Services. Speed up your development process and save money by implemeting solutions for your busniess using latest technologies to improve efficiency</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Serverless Systems</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/serverless-systems.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Serverless Systems" /><published>2020-07-01T18:37:13+04:00</published><updated>2020-07-01T18:37:13+04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/serverless-systems</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/serverless-systems.html">&lt;h4&gt;Why Serverless?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To fully understand why first we need to know the how what’s the different from normal systems that we generally understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;What is serverless?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serverless is a type of cloud computing execution model where the provider will dynamically manage the allocation of the resource required. Running your application on serverless means that it runs in stateless compute, either event driven or ephemeral, the best part that it’s fully managed by the cloud provider.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The present has been constantly changing and improving technologies that are becoming more available to any end to end consumer, building your applications before such technologies would require much more resources such hardware and engineers that can be more time consuming and costly, having the accessibility to not focus on infrastructure and focus more on the application can result to a faster development and deploying your application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Why should I consider Serverless Systems?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serverless Systems can Guarantee you some of the highest availability for the cost required, since you do not need to think about infrastructure and maintenance, global availability and scalability which are quite of time consuming you are able to prototype or test your application in an agile manner and less time consuming.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Fiott</name></author><category term="technologies" /><category term="services" /><summary type="html">Why Serverless? To fully understand why first we need to know the how what’s the different from normal systems that we generally understand.</summary></entry></feed>